A Back to the Future documentary
Back in Time is a documentary film directed by Jason Aron.
Cast, crew and fans explore the 'Back to the Future' time-travel trilogy's resonance
throughout our culture—30 years after Marty McFly went back in time.
Self, played by Michael J. Fox.
Self, played by Lea Thompson.
Self, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Self, played by Robert Zemeckis.
Self, played by Alan Silvestri.
Self, played by Bob Gale.
Back in Time is a 2015 American documentary film directed by Jason Aron.
The film explores the production, impact, and legacy of the Back to the Future film series, and includes interviews
with members of the series' cast and crew, including Robert Zemeckis, Steven Spielberg, Michael J.
Fox and Christopher Lloyd, as well as fans of the franchise.
The film explores themes of interview, filmmaking,
retrospective, fandom, film production.